Mohamed A.El-moniem

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Executive Summary

Versatile Front-End Developer with 2+ years of experience implementing complex web apps and frameworks, specializing in Javascript, React, and Angular, and passionate to learn new technologies.

Areas of Expertise

- HTML / CSS.
- · SCSS.
- · Javascript.
- Angular 11.
- React.
- Reactnative.
- Responsive Design.
- Wordpress.
- · NodeJs.
- Version Control Systems (GIT).
- cmd

Reach me at:

Address: Cairo, Egypt. phone: <u>+201111798451</u>. Site: <u>mon3m.com</u>
Emgil: dev@mon3m.com

Education & Training

faculty of science (2015 - present).

Work Experience

FAHMAWY, FRONT-END DEVELOPER

August 2019 - June 2021

- Built +15 WordPress sites, Using Custom UI and Implementing Themes.
- Collaborated with backend developers providing robust RESTful APIs.
- Developed some PHP & JS functions in WordPress to make sites suit the client's needs.
- Created a dashboard for managing co-working space reservations using angular.
- made react-native payment integration with hyper pays payment gateway.
- Handled client's requests and inquiries providing a superb service.

FREELANCE FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Jan 2021 - Present

- Started developing an e-commerce application and its dashboard for makeup and women stuff using Angular 11.
- Built fully functional E-Commerce websites using WordPress. <u>tycoon-realestate.com</u> - <u>diwanschool.com</u> - <u>treclo.com</u> - <u>dilfana.com</u> - <u>trans2target.com</u> - <u>austazy.com</u> - <u>redlineeg.com</u>
- Created a javascript function to fetch data from an API to a file using nodejs.

DAFATER, FRONT-END DEVELOPER

August 2021 - Present

- Converted xd designs into fully functional web pages using html, css, and Js.
- Created reusable and independent components using native javascript.
- Used different tools and technologies like pug, gulp, and oop in javascript.